

Raghav Agrawal

8630422423

in

@raghavagrawal1998

()

@raghavrv98

Personal Profile

M agrawalraghav669@gmail.com

Passionate Front-end web developer with over 1 year of experience in creating and designing web pages in a test-driven environment. Proficient in JavaScript, HTML5, and CSS; plus modern javaScript library.

Technical Skills

Programming language

JavaScript

HTML

CSS

CSS framework

Bootstrap

JavaScript library

React

Redux

Key Skills

Requirement Gathering Maintenance

3rd party library integration

Education

GLA University

B.Tech | CSE (**2016 - 2020**) CGPA - 7.67

Vidya Devi Jindal School

Intermediate - 74.8% High School - 8.4 CGPA

Career Summary

Front End Developer

(June 2020 - Present)

IOT83, Gurgaon, Haryana

Front End Developer (Intern)

(July 2019 - June 2020)

IOT83, Gurgaon, Haryana

Projects:

- 1. PMMP (Pipeline Management and Manufacture Program).
- 2. RS (Raychem Supervisor).

Responsibilities:

- Primarily focused on developing user interface components and implementing them following well-known React.js workflows (such as Redux).
- Build rich data-driven web pages by consuming RESTful services and APIs.
- Build highly-interactive web pages using modern web technologies such as JavaScript, HTML5, CSS.
- Actively participated in design and code reviews, to build robust applications.

Key Acheivements:

- Achieved timely delivery of all the goals in an effective & quality-bound manner.
- Developed projects in an agile manner and successfully delivered the sprint.

Projects

Le Thoos (www.lethoos.com)

Le Thoos is a food delivery service. It provides information, menus, and food delivery options from partner restaurants in select areas in Kosi Kalan.

AtoZonlinemart (www.atozonlinemart.com)

AtoZonlinemart is an online household products catalog. The primary motive is to provide products found in convenience stores, home essentials, and food supplies to its customers at lower cost.